<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MU88 - Spin Wheel</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <!--FONT-->
    <string name="font_italic" translatable="false">fonts/Roboto-BlackItalic.ttf</string>
    <string name="font_bold" translatable="false">fonts/Roboto-Bold.ttf</string>
    <string name="font_regular" translatable="false">fonts/Roboto-Regular.ttf</string>
    <string name="font_black" translatable="false">fonts/Roboto-Black.ttf</string>
    <string name="font_medium" translatable="false">font/Roboto-Medium.ttf</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="copy_to_clib_board">Save to clip board</string>
    <string name="app_name_setting">Spin Wheel</string>
    <string name="sound">Sound</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="active_all">Active all</string>
    <string name="inactive">Inactive</string>
    <string name="content">Content</string>
    <string name="loading_api">Getting the language for you</string>

    <string name="title_default_1">What I want to eat is..</string>
    <string name="content_default_1" translatable="false">Phone</string>
    <string name="content_default_2" translatable="false">Moto</string>
    <string name="content_default_3" translatable="false">Car</string>
    <string name="content_default_4" translatable="false">Big Gift</string>
    <string name="content_default_5" translatable="false">Kiss</string>
    <string name="content_default_6" translatable="false">One chicken</string>

    <string name="title_make_video_call">Make Voice Call</string>
    <string name="call_now">Call Now</string>
    <string name="call_type">Call type</string>
    <string name="incoming_call">Incoming call</string>
    <string name="calling">Calling</string>
    <string name="name_your_friend">Name Your Friend</string>
    <string name="hint_text_name">Cameron Williamson</string>
    <string name="please_fill_in_the_information">Please fill in the information</string>
    <string name="incoming_call_picture">Incoming call picture</string>
    <string name="video_of_incoming_calls">Video of incoming calls</string>
    <string name="call_later">Call later</string>
    <string name="now">Now</string>
    <string name="time_call_seconds">%s seconds</string>
    <string name="time_call_minutes">%s minutes</string>
    <string name="time_call_one_minutes">1 minute</string>
    <string name="send_later">Send later</string>
    <string name="pick_up_later">Pick up later</string>
    <string name="voice_later">Voice later</string>
    <string name="note">Note</string>
    <string name="note_title_error">Please fill out the \ninformation completely</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="maxium_characters">Maximum of 25 characters</string>
    <string name="error_link_video">Can\'t get video link.\n Please choose another video</string>
    <string name="title_calling">Calling...</string>

    <string name="message">Messenger</string>
    <string name="video_call_on_messenger">Video call on messenger</string>
    <string name="refuse">REFUSE</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer</string>

    <string name="outgoing_call_pictures">Outgoing call pictures</string>
    <string name="change_picture">Change picture</string>
    <string name="pick_up_the_phone_later">Pick up the phone later</string>
    <string name="make_voice_call_title">Make Voice Call</string>
    <string name="notification_type">Notification type</string>
    <string name="top">Top</string>
    <string name="popup">Popup</string>
    <string name="message_photo">Message photo</string>
    <string name="enter_message">Enter message</string>
    <string name="send_a_message_later">Send a message later</string>
    <string name="make_notification_title">Make Notification</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>

    <string name="dialog_comment_title">Comment box</string>
    <string name="input_title_phone">Số điện thoại: </string>
    <string name="input_title_content">Nội dung: </string>
    <string name="error_input">Sai định dạng số điện thoại.</string>
    <string name="send">Gửi</string>

    <string name="intro">QH88 là một ứng dụng công cụ hữu ích được thiết kế để giúp người dùng trong nhiều lĩnh vực khác nhau. Với nhiều tính năng đa dạng và dễ sử dụng, QH88 đem lại cho người dùng một trải nghiệm tuyệt vời và hiệu quả.

        Ứng dụng QH88 cung cấp cho người dùng một loạt các công cụ để giải quyết các vấn đề. Với chức năng tìm kiếm thông minh, người dùng có thể tìm kiếm thông tin về các bài viết, các bài hướng dẫn hay các video hướng dẫn cụ thể về cách giải quyết các vấn đề, Ngoài ra, QH88 còn có tính năng tương tác với những chuyên gia trong lĩnh vực để giúp người dùng tìm ra giải pháp tốt nhất cho vấn đề của họ.

        QH88 cũng cung cấp cho người dùng các công cụ để quản lý dữ liệu. Với tính năng lưu trữ và chia sẻ tập tin trực tuyến, người dùng có thể dễ dàng quản lý tài liệu của mình, bao gồm các tài liệu tập tin văn bản, hình ảnh, video hay tài liệu âm thanh. Ngoài ra, QH88 còn cung cấp cho người dùng tính năng backup và phục hồi tập tin, giúp bảo vệ dữ liệu của họ một cách an toàn.

        Bên cạnh đó, QH88 còn cung cấp cho người dùng các công cụ quản lý thời gian hiệu quả. Tính năng nhắc nhở và lịch biểu giúp người dùng quản lý thời gian của họ một cách có khoa học, giúp nâng cao tính hiệu quả trong công việc, học tập hay là trong cuộc sống hằng ngày. Với những tính năng đa dạng và tiện ích, QH88 đem lại cho người dùng một trải nghiệm hoàn hảo.

    </string>

    <string name="email_feedback">Hòm thư góp ý</string>
    <string name="verify_phone_number">Xác minh số điện thoại</string>
    <string name="view_home">View home</string>
    <string name="error_request_data">Lỗi server!</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>

    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="about_app">About App</string>
    <string name="guide">Guide</string>
    <string name="more_app">More App</string>
    <string name="rate_app">Rate App</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="contac_us">Contac us</string>

    <string name="again">Again</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="suggest">Suggest</string>
    <string name="your_content">Your Content</string>

    <string name="title_privacy">We built the Spin wheel app as a Free app.</string>
    <string name="content_privacy">This SERVICE is provided by Us at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.
The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service.I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
- Images: We are not responsible for the image content created by users or searched on the internet.
- Stories: User-generated stories in the app for political, offensive, or deceptive purposes.
- We are not responsible when users of the application for malicious purposes, political purposes, vote, and violate applicable national laws.
1. Information Collection and Use
For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information.The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
Links to the privacy policies of third party service providers can be used in the app

2. Log Data
I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data.
This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.

3. Cookies
Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers.
These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device\'s internal memory.
This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.

4. Service Providers
The permissions we use in the application:
android.permission.WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE

android.permission.READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE

android.permission.WAKE_LOCK

android.permission.VIBRATE

android.permission.INTERNET

android.permission.ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE

android.permission.RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED

NOTE:
- We are committed to using the above rights only for the purpose of serving the function of the application and fully comply with the policies of google play and not for any other purpose.

- All information provided by users will only be stored on their device and we do not collect and store it in any form (including on servers or on cloud services...).

- We do not disclose, store or share any sensitive information of users (email, bank account...).

- Any questions or complaints please contact us via email: support@outlookdaily.co

5. Service Providers
I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;

To provide the Service on our behalf;

To perform Service-related services;
To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information.
The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf.However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.

6. Security
I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it.
But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security.

7. Links to Other Sites
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site.
Note that these external sites are not operated by me.Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites.

I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

8. Children’s Privacy
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13.
In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers.
If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to take necessary actions.

9. Changes to This Privacy Policy
I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time.Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes.
I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

10. Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at support@outlookdaily.co
    </string>

    <string name="hint_edit_spin">Ex: Museum</string>
    <string name="cancel_dialog">Cancel</string>
    <string name="error_character">Maximum of 14 characters</string>
    <string name="name_content">Name Content</string>
    <string name="spin_theme">Spin theme</string>
    <string name="empty_view">Please add content at the\n button below</string>
    <string name="add_content">Add Content</string>
    <string name="error_same_name">This content already exists. Please enter other content!</string>
    <string name="error_blank_content">Content cannot be left blank</string>
    <string name="delete_this_content">Delete this content</string>
    <string name="error_min_content">Minimum amount of content is 4.\nPlease fill in more</string>
    <string name="error_max_content">You have reached your limit on\nthe amount of content.\nPlease upgrade for more choices.</string>
    <string name="error_max_content_in_app">You have reached your limit on the amount of content.</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="error_blank_question">Please fill in the question information</string>
    <string name="full_color">Full color</string>
    <string name="green_color">Green</string>
    <string name="red_color">Red</string>
    <string name="blue_color">Blue</string>
    <string name="purple_color">Purple</string>
    <string name="yellow_color">Yellow</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

</resources>